嘿 伙计 我忘记密码了 让我进去
Hey, dude, I don't remember the password. Let me in.
我觉得有人在跟踪我
I think someone's following me.
谁
Who?
快进来 这是纪录片的工作人员
Get in here. It's the doc crew.
你也是 快进来
You, too. Come on.
当我逃离南多的时候
When I ran away from Nandor,
我真的不知道该去哪里
I didn't really know where to go.
吉列尔莫
Guillermo!
所以我飞啊飞 飞了好几个小时
So I just flew for hours and hours.
这有点酷 因为这是
Which was a little cool because
我以蝙蝠的模样呆得最久的一次了
that was the longest I've ever stayed a bat.
但也不酷
But also not cool
因为我知道南多在想方设法
because I knew Nandor was trying
找到我 然后杀了我
to track me down to kill me.
最后 我去找了德里克 因为
Eventually, I just went to Derek because...
我没有其他可以求助的人了
I had no one else to turn to.
我一直低调行事
I've just been laying low,
不知道躲了多久
hiding for who knows how long.
此处希望有掌声
I wish they had Bravo here.
想要活得长久可千万不要唱出来
♪ Don't sing if you want to live long ♪
他们毫无用处
♪ They have no use for your song ♪
你死了*3
♪ You're dead, you're dead, you're dead ♪
你死了 早已不在这世上
♪ You're dead and out of this world ♪
如今你的希望和怜悯之心都没了
♪ Now your hope and compassion is gone ♪
连你的梦想也销售殆尽
♪ You sold out your dream to the world ♪
毫无生气*3
♪ Stay dead, stay dead, stay dead ♪
你死了 早已不在这世上
♪ You're dead and out of this world. ♪
新浪微博 @摆渡字幕组 翻译
关注微博 了解最新影视资源
字幕组翻译人员招募中报名群:397129952
追美剧 用豆芽美剧app 下载地址：MY8.COOL
《吸血鬼生活》第五季第10集
翻译：jayjayliu，吃仙贝吗
我觉得有辆货车在跟踪我 他们可能
I think there was a van tailing me, they may have been
-也在跟踪你 -德里克 是他们
tailing you, too. Derek, that was them.
哇哦
Whoa.
-你们很棒 向你们致敬 -德里克 向我保证
You guys are good. Respect. Derek, just promise me
你还没告诉别人我在这里
you haven't told anyone else that I'm here.
吉列尔莫 我能告诉谁 说真的 我的邻居查德吗
Guillermo, who would I tell? Literally. My neighbor Chad?
因为... 是的 我是告诉了查德
Because... yes, actually, I did tell Chad.
我是认真的 好吗
This is serious, okay?
我的主人想要杀了我
My master is actively trying to kill me.
你把我的肉汉堡带来了吗
Did you bring my meat?
带来了 汉堡 三分熟 照你要求的那样
Yes, burgers, extra rare, just like you asked.
我对收银员施了催眠术 这样就没花我一分钱
I tried hypnosis on the cashier so I could get them for free.
事实证明 我不擅长这个
Turns out, I'm bad at it.
Venmo是Paypal推出的一款应用软件,可以用于朋友间转账以及电商平台上的消费。
Zelle是一个美国银行间的即时转账系统。
我不知道你用不用Venmo支付
So, um, I don't know if you use Venmo
还是说你喜欢用Zelle转账…
or maybe you're a Zelle guy...
这些根本不是生的
These are not raw.
我能感觉到这肉一定烤过了 德里克
I can taste that they've kissed the grill, Derek.
-你好吗 贱人 -你来这里干什么
Sup, bitch? What the hell are you doing here?
有人看见你吗 赶紧进来
Did anyone see you? Get inside.
没有 就算有人跟踪也没关系
No, and it wouldn't matter if they did
因为 看见没 我乔装打扮了一番
because, hello, I'm in disguise.
别跳了 赶紧进来
Stop dancing, get inside.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
你朋友德里克告诉我你藏在哪了
Your friend Derek told me where you were hiding.
我今天早些时候
I paid him a little visit
去拜访了他一下  看出来了吗
earlier today, see?
原来是你
So, that was you.
你以为是谁
Who did you think it was?
她告诉我她叫侦探警察
She told me her name was Detective Policeman.
-真好笑 -我需要你帮我个忙 伙计
That's funny. I'm gonna need you to do me a favor, buddy.
你能去市场给我买点生的 我要生的肉
Can you go to the market and get me some raw, raw meat
然后保证不会告诉任何人我在哪儿吗
and make sure you don't tell anyone where I'm at.
-你能做到吗 -能做到 能做到
Can you do that? Can do, can do.
-谢谢你 伙计 -好嘞
Thank you, buddy. Okay, great.
-好的 非常感谢 -一会儿见
Okay. Thanks so much. See you guys in a minute.
白痴
Idiot.
吉列尔莫 坐下
Guillermo. Sit.
你不能对转化你的吸血鬼
You simply cannot talk to the vampire who turned you
如此不尊重地说话
with such disrespect.
这是一种神圣的关系
That is a sacred relationship.
你得保护他
You have to protect him.
就像我们保护男爵和陛下一样
Like we protect the Baron and the Sire.
如果那个蠢货出了什么事
If anything was to happen to that stupid man,
对你来说 我的朋友 影响将是灾难性的
the effects for you, my friend, would be catastrophic.
你说的对
Yes.
对不起 我不该那样跟德里克说话
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have spoken to Derek like that.
我只是有点紧张 你知道的
I'm just a little bit on edge with the whole, you know--
南多想杀了你
Nandor trying to kill you thing.
-是有点尴尬 -顺便问一句 呃…
Awkward. Which, by the way, um...
那边有什么进展吗
Any progress on that end?
呃 有一点
Uh, yeah, um, a little.
- 你和他谈过了 -是的
You talked to him? Yeah.
他说什么了
What'd he say?
南多 别这样
Nandor, come on.
我要杀了他
I'm gonna murder him!
也许我给他写封信..
Maybe if I write him a letter...
是啊 如果你给他写了封遗书
Yeah, like if you wrote him a suicide note,
并且真的贯彻执行
and actually followed through on it,
那样可能会让他冷静下来
then that would probably cool him down.
哇 他们也太全情投入了 不是吗
Wow. They're really going at it, aren't they?
我为什么要这么做
Why did I do this?
听着 感情是会变的
Look, relationships evolve.
就像我和那些在餐厅工作的安提帕克森人
Like me and those Antipaxon people who work at the diner.
一开始 我只是用他们来摆脱我的魔咒
At first, I was just using them to get rid of my hex.
但后来发现..
But then it turned out...
我真的很喜欢和他们一起玩
I really like hanging out with those guys.
我知道你不是有意…
I know you didn't mean...
我知道你不是有意
I know you didn't mean
让事情发展成这样的
for things to turn out this way,
但我觉得你
but I think it's time
是时候接受了... 你知道吗
you need to accept-- You know what?
等等 我再也受不了了
Hang on, I cannot take this anymore!
这很难 你知道的
It's hard, you know.
知道自己做了什么
To know that you've done something,
你把事情搞砸了却无法..
that you messed up but you can't...
挽回 然后…
...fix it and...
她也加入他们了
And she's joined them.
我在狩猎 夜复一夜地
Night after night, I hunt.
我不能休息 直到吉列尔莫咽下最后一口气
I cannot rest until Guillermo has taken his last breath
他的骨头在我的靴子下嘎吱作响为止
and I feel his bones crunch under my boots.
所以我一直在监视一个地方
So I've been watching the one place
我知道他最终会回到..
I know he will return to eventually...
帕纳拉面包
Panera Bread.
我抓到你了
I've got you now.
他可以跑
He can run,
但他跑不远
but he cannot run far.
因为他的腿很短
Because he has very short legs.
吉列尔莫 你死定了
Guillermo, now you will die.
我什么都没做
-I-I didn't do anything.
那些背叛我的人会付出代价的 吉列尔莫
Those that betray me will pay the ultimate price, Guillermo.
还有这个伪装
And this disguise
它能稍微改变你的外表
that has slightly altered your appearance
但它骗不了我
does not fool me.
我不是吉列尔莫 我不是吉列尔莫
I'm not Guillermo! I'm not Guillermo!
我是帕顿·奥斯沃特 我是个演员
I'm Patton Oswalt. I'm an actor.
-帕顿·奥斯沃特 -是的
Patton Oswalt? Yeah.
-演员 -没错
An actor? Yes!
我怎么会认识你
What would I know you from?
-我有演《料理鼠王》 -那是电影吗
I was in Ratatouille. Is that a movie?
是动画片
It's... It was animated.
我是老鼠的配音
I was the voice of a rat.
我更喜欢真人表演
I prefer live action. Uh...
你认识约翰 · 斯莱特里吗
Do you know John Slattery?
我不认识他 但我听说过他
I don't know him personally, I know of him.
-他看起来很酷 -他就是很酷
He seems really cool. He is.
是的 我要晕过去了
Yes, I-I'm gonna pass out...
抱歉 帕顿·奥斯沃特
My apologies, Patton Oswalt.
你很有礼貌 不像吉列尔莫
You are respectful, unlike Guillermo.
我一直在那边那栋楼的
I have been lying in wait for him
楼顶埋伏着等他
on the top of that building there.
他回到帕纳拉面包店
It's only a matter of time
只是时间问题
before he returns to Panera Bread,
就像羚羊回到他的水坑一样
like a gazelle to his watering hole.
他一回来 我就动手
And when he does, I will strike.
你确定是这家帕纳拉面包吗
Are you sure it's that Panera Bread?
-你什么意思 -这里有很多家帕纳拉面包
What do you mean? There's a lot of Panera Breads.
它们... 它们遍布全城
They're... They're all over the city.
该死
Shit.
-哪位 -小吉
Who is it? Gigi?
-你好呀 -你在这里做什么
Hello. What are you doing here?
-你怎么找到我的 -哦 我刚..
How did you find me? Oh, I just...
拿了一张斯塔顿岛的地图把它放在一个网格上
took a map of Staten Island and laid it over a grid
找所有和阿比快餐店 派对商店或者毛衣店
and looked for any motel that shared a square
共用一个广场的汽车旅馆
with an Arby's, a party store or a sweater shop.
这些东西我都没靠近过
Well, I'm not near any of those things.
我知道 所以我就问了娜嘉
Yeah, I know, so I just asked Nadja.
好极了 你想要我怎样
Great. What do you want?
首先 我想祝你好运
First off, I just want to wish you good luck.
你是个陷入困境的好人
You're a nice enough guy caught in a bad sitch.
我想我们都没想到你会有这样的结果
I-I don't think any of us were hoping for this outcome for you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
其次 我是来给你做离职面谈的
Secondly, I am here to conduct your exit interview,
从你的工作 作为一个熟悉你的人
from your job as a familiar.
还有你的生活 所以..
And also your life, so...
请坐 我不想占用你太多时间
Have a seat. I don't want to take up too much of your time,
我知道它很宝贵
I know it's valuable.
因为已经所剩无几了
Because there's so little of it left.
好了
Okay.
“南多的随从”离职面谈 晚上十点四十七分
Familiar exit interview, 10:47 p.M.,
由科林·罗宾逊主持
Colin Robinson conducting interview.
德拉·“克鲁兹”先生
Um, Mr. De la "Cruzz,"
是什么促使你离职的
what's prompting you to leave your job?
是南多 他想杀我
Nandor trying to kill me.
那么... 作为随从 你的薪水是多少
And... what was your salary as a familiar?
我没有报酬
Oh, I don't get paid.
这样不行 坦白说 为了面谈能继续进行下去
No, but honestly, for this to work,
我需要一个大概的数字
I kind of need a ballpark figure.
500美元 或者550美元一周的样子
$500, $550 a week?
-我没有报酬 -嗯哼
I don't get paid. -Uh-huh.
你觉得我们还能继续
And do you think we can get away with
不付钱给下一个人吗
not paying the next person?
好了 面谈结束
Okay. This interview's over.
面谈结束
Interview concluded by subject
受试者很合作 有时甚至能说是口齿伶俐
who was cooperative and at times almost articulate.
好了 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
这是我个人送你的
This is just from me.
有你在家里真好
It was nice having you in the house.
谢谢你 科林
Thanks, Colin.
“ 杰伊·斯蒂克 第四季度销售主管 1977年”
"Jay Sturkel, Quarter Four Sales Leader, 1977."
我在房地产拍卖会上买的 不过你懂我的意思就行
I got it at estate sale, but y-you get the drift.
-恭喜你 -谢谢
Congratulations. Thank you.
我觉得最让我恼火的是
I think what bugs me the most
我把我的友谊给了吉列尔莫
is that I have given Guillermo my friendship.
这是我不会随便给别人的礼物
This is a gift I do not give to just anyone.
你知道 友谊是需要... 努力争取的
Uh, you know, friendship has to be... earned.
你的..
How is your, um...
-火鸡培根布拉沃 -没错
Turkey Bacon Bravo. Yes.
很好吃
It is, it's good.
我通常在这里拿面包碗……
And I usually get the bread bowls here--
我觉得是
I think what it is
吉列尔莫自作自受
is that I thought Guillermo had earned it.
你是个很好的倾听者 帕顿·奥斯沃特
You are a good listener, Patton Oswalt.
你知道 这很有趣 因为几年前
You know, it's funny because something like this
我和我的经纪人也发生过类似的事 我们..
happened with me a couple years ago with my manager, we--
嘘 听我说
Shh. Just listen. Oh...
我们现在不是在说你
We are not talking about you right now,
我们有吗 帕顿·奥斯沃特
are we, Patton Oswalt?
不 我们没有
No, we're not. Mm.
-请继续说 -谢谢
So, go on. Thank you.
哪位
Who is it?
客房服务
Housekeeping.
-我是不是应该问问你是怎么找到... -嘘 嘘
I should ask how you found out where-- Shh, shh.
什么
What?
我猜你对你的..
I'm guessing you're content with your...
厕纸状况很满意吧
toilet paper situation?
是的 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
好的
All right.
那我就..
Then I will...
不打扰你晚上看电视了
leave you to watch the television for the evening.
跟你说声... 晚安了
And I will say... goodbye.
-坐下 -发生什么事了
Sit down. What's going on?
我必须道歉 吉尔莫 我觉得我让你失望了
I must apologize, Gizmo, I feel like I've let you down.
所有那些科学实验
All those science experiments,
它们只是一条死胡同
they were nothing but a blind alley.
拉兹洛 你已经尽力了
Laszlo, you tried your best.
不 有些事我..
No, there's been something I...
你应该换一个
You-you should probably put something on
比这个声音再大一点的
that's a bit louder than this.
不然它都盖不过我们的声音
Otherwise, it won't drown our voices out.
这样好多了
That's better.
我在你还是个年轻的随从的时候就认识你了
I've known you since you were a young familiar.
过去我可能对你很严厉
And I may have been hard on you in the past,
然后..
and, uh...
你能不能换一个..
Could you put something that...
声音一样大 但敲击声更小点的
is as loud but less percussive?
体育 好的 这样就好多了
Sport, yes, that's better.
我说 那东西里有没有..
And I say, does that thing have any...
成人节目
programs of the adult variety?
呃 应该有的
Uh, I suppose, yeah.
这样可以了吧
There you go.
你刚才说什么
You were saying?
什么
Sorry?
-你刚才说什么 -哦对了
You were saying? Yes.
我是说..
I was saying...
我认识你的时候 你还是..
I've known you since you were...
一个年轻的随…
a young fa...
你觉得他们会怎么做
What do you think they're gonna do?
-拉兹洛 -- 好的 好的
-Yeah, Laszlo-- Yes, yes,
抱歉 从你还是一个年轻的随从的时候开始
s-sorry, since you were a young familiar.
我现在要告诉你一些
And, uh, I'm about to tell you something now
我从来没有告诉过别人的事
that I've never told anyone else before.
-拉 拉兹洛 -我的天哪
-L-Laszlo? Good grief.
你要告诉我一些
You were going to tell me something
-你以前从没告诉过任何人的...  -嘘
you never told anyone before...? Shh.
你可能得给我点时间
You might have to give me a minute.
所以 是的 连拉兹洛也来过了
So, yeah, even Laszlo came by.
如果我知道..
If I would've known how...
我最后的几天会怎样
my last couple of days would play out,
最后的几个月会怎样..
how the last couple of months...
我就不会让德里克把我变成吸血鬼了
I would've never asked Derek to turn me.
不是我不想死
It's not that I don't want to die,
相信我 我真的 真的不想死
and trust me, I really, really don't want to die,
但我更害怕失去这群吸血鬼
but I'm just more afraid of losing the vampires.
我的朋友们
My friends.
我一直觉得如果我变成了吸血鬼
I always figured if I got turned into a vampire
这会让我更接近他们
that it would... bring me closer to them.
但却让我感到前所未有的孤独
But it's just left me feeling more alone than ever.
南多 我能问你个问题吗
Nandor, can I ask you a question?
可以 帕顿·奥斯沃特
Yes, Patton Oswalt.
你和吉列尔莫的友谊很特别 对吧
Your friendship with Guillermo is very special, right?
我以为是
I thought it was.
我打赌..
And I bet...
去杀一个朋友
killing a friend...
感觉一定很痛苦
would really hurt.
我想这将是一个人
I imagine it would be one of the worst feelings
最糟糕的感受之一
a person could have.
所以 如果你..
So, what if you...
去修复这段友谊呢
repair the friendship?
-你去修复它 -所以你的意思是
-You repair it-- So you're saying
我不该去杀我曾经的朋友吗
that I should not kill my former friend?
- 是的 你...-这就是你的建议吗
-Uh, yes, you-you-- This is your suggestion?
你知道 你去重建..
Well, you know, you rebuild--
在听了我充满欺骗和背叛的故事之后
After hearing my tale of deceit and betrayal?
所有背叛我的人都必须被毁灭
All that betray me must be destroyed.
- 等等 等等 -再见 帕顿·奥斯沃特
-Wait, wait-- Goodbye, Patton Oswalt.
不过他说得很有道理
He does make a good point, though.
胳膊 还有一块..
...arm, and a block of--
终于
Of course.
嗨 我是来向你表示哀悼的
Hi. I just came by to pay you my condolences.
“对你失去的生命表示遗憾”
"Sorry for your loss of your life."
还有人不知道我在这里吗
Is there anyone who doesn't know that I'm here?
我通常是最后一个知道的 所以可能没有人不知道了
Well, I'm usually the last one to know, so probably not.
谢谢
Thank you. Yeah.
然后我还带来了一些朋友
And then I also brought some friends
他们想跟我告别
who wanted to say goodbye.
嗨 爸爸
Hiya, Daddy.
嘿 导游小姐说你要去一个
Hey. Guide lady said you're going off
-又大又漂亮的... -嘿 大家伙
to a big, beautiful... Hey, big guy.
空中农场
...farm in the sky.
我们能去吗
Can we come? Oh...
不行 伙计
No, buddy. Aw.
农场没多余的地方了
There's no room at the farm.
”随着一个好人的离去
"In the death of a good man,
我们透过时间可以看到永恒
eternity is seen looking through time."
约翰·沃尔夫冈·冯·歌德
Johann Wolfgang von Goethe.
好吧
Okay.
- 所以...-哦
-So-- Oh.
抱歉
Sorry.
你好啊 妈妈
Hola, Ma.
你好啊 吉列尔莫
Hello, Guillermo.
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.
你在哪
Where are you?
我就在这跟你妈妈聊得正开心呢
Oh, I'm right here having a nice conversation with your mother.
在她的公寓里 她住的地方
In her apartment. Where she lives.
我妈妈和这事没关系
My mother has nothing to do with this.
如果你敢碰她 我发誓..
If you touch her, I swear...
既然你知道我在哪儿 你为什么不过来一下
Well, you know where I am. Why don't you come over here
我们可以讨论一下接下来的事情
and we can discuss what happens next.
-我得走了 -再见 爸爸
I have to go. Bye, Daddy.
你已经退房了吗 还是我们可以继续待在这里
Have you checked out already? Or is it okay if we hang here?
他不会回来了
He's not coming back.
快点 你个愚蠢的…
Ah, come on, you stupid...
-离她远点 -吉列尔莫
Get away from her. Guillermo.
我待会再过来 好吗
I'll be back, okay?
¿你好吗 儿子?
¿Cómo está, mijo?
嘿 妈妈
Hey, Mami. Mwah.
别太久咯 西尔维娅
Don't be long, Sylvia.
我还是想看看吉列尔莫
Still want to see the photographs of Guillermo
在这个哥特式阶段的照片
in this gotico phase.
你可以杀了我
You can kill me if you want,
但别把她扯进来 好吗
but you leave her out of this, okay?
我知道我可以杀了你
Oh, I know I could kill you.
这是你活该
And you'd deserve it.
但我决定不这么做
But I have decided not to.
我不相信你
Yeah, well, I don't believe you.
你当然不信
No, of course you don't.
但最近发生了一些事
But something happened recently and...
让我改变了主意
it's made me change my mind.
- 哦 是吗  什么事  -我的朋友帕顿·奥斯沃特
Oh, yeah? What? My friend Patton Oswalt.
他突然去世了 然后..
He passed away quite suddenly. And, um...
失去朋友的感觉很难受
it didn't feel good losing a friend.
我怎么知道你说的是真的
How do I know you're telling the truth?
因为我以吸血鬼的身份向你保证
Because I give you my word as a vampire.
-还不够  -那我以战士的身份…
Not good enough. Then I give you my word...
向你保证
as a warrior.
如果我在撒谎
"If I'm lying...
现在就杀了我
...then kill me now."
那就这么定了
Then it is settled.
你会活着跟我回家
You'll come home with me, alive.
妈妈 不要
Mami, no!
哇 成功了
Wow, that worked.
-嗯  - 嗯
Mm? Hmm?
我们带来了消息
We return with news.
我不打算再杀吉列尔莫了
I no longer plan to kill Guillermo.
耶 耶
Yay. Yay.
他会和我们住在一个屋檐下
He will live here in this house, with us,
平起平坐
as an equal.
作为一个吸血鬼
As a vampire.
我们以前是四个 现在是五个
Boo. Where once we were four, we are now five.
我觉得你的数学有问题
I think your math is off.
如果我知道吉尔莫会和我们在一起
If I had known Gizmo was going to stay with us,
我会说直接杀了他 一了百了
I would've said just kill him and be done with it.
他要坐在哪里
Where is he going to sit?
我不会让座的 所以他会坐哪儿
I-I'm not giving up my seat. So where is he going to sit?
等等 吉尔莫不能完全变成吸血鬼
Hold on a second. Gizmo cannot fully become a vampire
因为他有范海辛的血
due to his Van Helsing blood.
拉兹洛 拉兹洛,
Laszlo, Laszlo,
你做了那么多实验和笔记
with all your experiments and your notetaking,
还有你那些怪异的混血怪物
and your weird-ass, hybrid freaks,
你从没想过最简单的解决办法
you never thought of the simplest solution.
- 是什么  -你从没让吉列尔莫喝过人血
Which is? You never got Guillermo to drink human blood.
- 等等 你从没想过吗  -闭嘴
-Wait. Y-You never thought of that? Shut up.
- 我觉得我做不到  -你必须做到
I don't think I can do this. You must.
否则你会被永远困在
Or else you'll be eternally frozen
在这无尽的痛苦地狱边缘 现在喝吧
in this painful, unending limbo. Now drink.
喝吧 吉列尔莫
Come on, Guillermo.
喝吧 贱人 喝吧 贱人
Drink, bitch. Yeah, drink it, bitch.
是的 喝下去 全部吞下去
Yes. Drink it. Swallow it all.
喝吧 喝吧 喝光光
Drink. Drink. Suck on it, baby. Come on, drink!
喝
Oi, drink.
喝 喝 喝 像个男人一样喝
Drink. Drink. Drink it. Take it like a man.
尖牙
Fangs.
哇 啊
Wow Ah.
我从未感觉如此活力四射
I've never felt more alive.
我早该想到的
I really should've thought of that.
我是吸血鬼了
I'm a vampire.
我是吸血鬼
I'm a vampire!
我是个吸血鬼
I'm a vampire! Yahoo.
是的
Yep.
干得漂亮
Nicely done.
才一小口血 他就像个玉米超人
One sip of blood and he's like Cornholio over here.
是的
Yes.
他喜欢这样
He likes that.
哦
Ooh.
看看我变成了什么
Behold what I've become.
是的 我们都经历过
Yes, yes, we've all been there.
为什么我们都坐着不动
Why are we all sitting on our asses?
我们做点什么吧 接下来怎么办
Let's do something! What do we do next?
拿扫帚来
Get a broom.
现在 我们去狩猎
Now, we hunt!
对不起 妈妈要吃东西
I'm sorry, Mommy needs to eat.
狩猎 狩猎 狩猎
Hunt, hunt, hunt!
狩猎 狩猎
Hunt, hunt!
聚会狂
Fomo.
这倒提醒了我
Which reminds me,
成为百万富翁最快的方法是什么
what's the fastest way to become a millionaire?
你以亿万富翁的身份开始 然后买下一家酒庄
You start as a billionaire and buy a winery.
只是说个关于酒的笑话
Just a little wine humor for you.
哦
Oh.
侍酒师是一个濒临灭绝的品种..
Sommeliers are a dying breed...
我吃太多了 我觉得不舒服
Oh. I've eaten too much. I feel sick.
继续 吉列尔莫
Go on, Guillermo.
我为你敲昏了他
I bonked this one on the head just for you.
他们更容易被吸干和杀死
They're much easier to drain and kill
不会扭来扭去
when they're not wriggling around.
不用了 我不是很饿
Oh, no, I-I'm actually not that hungry.
好吧 顺便说一句 如果你让他们昏迷
Okay, well, FYI, if you leave them hanging around too long
太久的话 他们的血液就会失去活力
when they're unconscious, their blood, it loses its zing.
我从没杀过人
I've never killed anyone before.
我是说 我杀过几十个吸血鬼
I mean, I guess dozens of vampires.
我确实把人类
And I did bring humans
带给吸血鬼 好让他们大开杀戒
to the vampires so they could kill them.
我肢解了
And I've dismembered,
一堆尸体
like, a ton of dead bodies.
但在餐厅里 那是个活生生的人
But back at the restaurant, that was a real living person.
当我靠近去吸..
And when I leaned in to take...
我可以..
I could...
闻到他们的洗发水
smell their shampoo
我一直在想
and all I kept thinking was
这家伙在便利店
this guy was at CVS
把洗发水都闻个遍
just sniffing away all these shampoos
然后说 我想我要买这个
and says, "Eh, I think I'll get this one
因为它让我想起了我小时候去露营的地方
because it reminds me of where I used to go camping as a kid."
我做不到 对不起 我们能不能..
I can't do this, I'm sorry. Could we...
我不能..
-I can't--
正如我所担心的
Just as I feared.
吉列尔莫不是做吸血鬼的料
Guillermo is not cut out to be a vampire.
我会解决的
I will fix.
你召唤我
You summoned me?
是的 我希望吉列尔莫..
Yes, I wish for Guillermo--
你的愿望早就用完了
Eh, eh, you ran out of wishes a long time ago.
你一直带着我吗
Have you just been carrying me around?
也许吧
Maybe.
是的
Yeah.
好吧
Okay, well...
很高兴再次见到你 你可以..
Nice to see you again. You can, uh...
我能活动一下腿吗
Can't I stretch my legs a little?
我也想帮你 但是..
I wish I could help you, but, uh...
真好笑 快进灯里去
That's very funny. Get in the fucking lamp.
我都不知道还有个特别的仪式
I didn't even know there was a special ceremony for...
等等 那个仪式叫什么来着
Wait, what was the ceremony called again?
吸血鬼变身仪式
The Ceremony of Vampiric Transmogrification.
别紧张
Oh. Don't be nervous,
我们都经历过
we have all been through it.
很吓人吗
Well, is it scary?
没有你处理不了的事
Nothing you cannot handle.
这个古老的仪式会加速你前进的步伐
The ancient ceremony will help hasten you along your path.
是时候了
It is time.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
准备好了
I am.
嘿
Hey.
德里克也在这里吗
Derek is here, too?
是的 该死的家伙
Yes. Fucking guy.
古老的仪式规定他必须在场
But ancient ritual dictates that he must be present.
来吧 大家好
Come on. Hey, everyone.
哈喽
Hello.
德里克 嘿
Derek. Hey.
所有的吸血鬼 我们在黑夜聚集于此
Vampires all, gather we here in the dark of night?
我们都来了
We do.
我们围成一个圈
We have made of ourselves a circle?
- 圈  -没有被破坏的圈
-The circle-- The circle unbroken. Unbroken.
我们在生与死的十字路口
We gather here in a circle unbroken
聚集成一个完整的圆圈
at the crossroads between life and death.
吉列尔莫·克鲁兹 你准备好了吗
Guillermo de la Cruz, are you prepared?
准备好了
I am.
吉列尔莫·克鲁兹 你头脑清醒
Guillermo de la Cruz, are you of sound mind
体魄强健吗
and strong of body?
是的
I am.
我们会做出选择
A choice will be made.
这个选择只能由你来做
This choice can only be made by you.
我们吸血鬼只是见证者
We vampires here are only witnesses.
主持人 准备火焰
Mistress of Ceremony, prepare the flames.
就是我
That's me.
干得漂亮
Nicely done.
吉列尔莫·克鲁兹 我现在问你一个问题
Guillermo de la Cruz, I will now ask you one question.
答案必须来自你的内心
The answer must come from your heart.
因为这是最后一次
For this is the last time
你可以做出最终选择的机会
you get to make this final choice.
- 听清楚了吗  -嗯
Do I make myself clear? -Mm-hmm.
你愿意做一个人类..
Would you rather be a human...
还是吸血鬼
...or vampire?
一个人类
A human.
如我所料
As I predicted.
不是我不想成为吸血鬼
It's not that I don't want to be a vampire,
我真的很想
I really, really do. Sure.
都是因为杀戮
It's all the killing.
细节不必多说 没关系
You can spare us the details, it's fine.
你想成为人类 这没什么好羞耻的
You want to be a human, there's no shame in that.
- 我们会帮你实现的  -等等 什么
We're gonna make it happen. Wait, what?
主持人 分发兜帽
Mistress of Ceremony, distribute the hoods.
又是我
That's me again.
你做得很好 谢谢你 德里克
You're doing a great job. Thank you, Derek.
- 我能要一个小点的...  -它们是通用尺寸
-Can I get a smaller-- They're unisex.
- 一个尺寸适合所有大小 好吧  -是的
It's a one size fits all situation? Okay. -Yep. Mm-hmm.
我该戴个兜帽 还是..
Do I get a hood, or...
快点 我也给你准备了一个
Hurry it up. I have one for you, too.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们蒙蔽自己 没有人能看见
We blind ourselves that none may witness.
大家戴上兜帽
Hoods on, everyone.
我们蒙蔽自己
♪ We blind ourselves ♪
没有人能看见
♪ That none may see. ♪
很好 去二号位置
Very nice. Proceed to position two.
不好意思 二号位置是什么
I'm sorry, w-what's position two?
就是你那里 德里克 没关系
Just as you are, Derek, that's fine.
-等等 什么  -这是唯一的办法 吉列尔莫
Wait, what? It is the only way, Guillermo.
- 我也会死吗  -不会
-W-Won't I die, too? No.
你会变回原来的样子
You'll go back to how you were when you were turned.
你很快就会长大一个月
You'll just get a month older really quickly.
肯定还有别的办法
There's got to be another way.
没有别的办法了
There's no other way.
这是唯一的办法
It is the only way.
-我做不到 -我就知道
I can't do this. Knew it.
不好意思 不能做什么 我错过了什么
I'm sorry, can't do what? What am I missing?
戴好兜帽 德里克 你做得很好
Just keep that hood on, Derek. You're doing great.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你想让我来吗
You want me to do it?
-我不知道  -我知道
I don't know. I do.
把那个给我
Give me that.
吉列尔莫 你没事吧
Guillermo, you okay?
哇哦 该死
Whoa! Um... Oh, shit.
一切都很模糊
Everything's kind of blurry.
我想我需要我的旧眼镜
I think I need my old glasses.
-给 -谢谢
Here. Thank you.
真好玩
Well, that was fun.
我们现在能把普通灯打开了吗
Can we turn the regular lights on now, please?
当然 谁能帮我把这些兜帽和长袍
Oh, sure. Can somebody help me pick up all these
都捡起来
hoods and robes?
别管了 加菲一会儿来拿
Eh, just leave them. Garfield will pick 'em up later.
我不得不说 这些横幅真是可爱
I must say, the, uh, the banners are a lovely touch.
我也喜欢
You know, I like them, too.
它们是什么意思
What do they mean?
说实话 我不知道 男爵
I don't know, to be honest, Baron.
我只是想要看起来酷酷的 诡异的东西
I just wanted something that looked cool and creepy.
-非常好 -是的
Very nice, yes.
家里还有个保姆在等我们 我们得走了
We have a sitter waiting at home, so we're gonna head out.
-慢走  -卡琳希塔 再见
Good evening. Kalinychta. Bye.
有人想玩飞行棋吗
Anyone up for a game of parcheesi?
还是看电影吧
Maybe a movie.
-我醉了 -《麦克马伦兄弟》
I'm zonked. The Brothers McMullin?
那根本不是什么真正的仪式 对吧
That wasn't even a real ceremony, was it?
不是
No.
我在阁楼的一个盒子里找到了长袍
I found the robes in a box in the attic and, uh...
从家得宝买的蜡烛
the candles I think we got from a Home Depot?
对不起 吉列尔莫
I'm sorry, Guillermo.
只有这样你才能搞清楚
It was the only way for you to figure out
你真正想要的东西
what you actually wanted.
这是个可怕而艰难的决定
It was a horrible and hard decision.
我觉得你做了正确的选择
I think you made the right choice.
我知道
I know.
现在 如果你不介意在日出之前
Now, if you wouldn't mind clearing up Derek's corpse
清理德里克的尸体 那就太好了
before sunrise, that would be great.
没关系 我来帮你
Its alright i"ll give you a hand.
谢谢 拉兹洛
Thanks, Laszlo.
-你拿包 我抱德里克  -好的
You take the bag, I'll take Derek. Okay.
来吧 老伙计 你最好去叫门
Come on, old chap. You better get the door.
巫师先生
Mr. Necromancer?
你有法术成功所需的
And you have the necessary items required
必要物品吗
for the procedure to succeed?
他说的是现金
He means the cash.
是的 这几乎是我给德里克的所有钱
Yeah, it was almost all the money I gave Derek
让他把我变成吸血鬼
to turn me into a vampire.
他只在Hot Topic潮牌购物网花了270美元
He only spent like $270 on "vampire clothes"
买了吸血鬼服装
that he got from Hot Topic.
你不用数了 都在这儿 巫师
You don't need to count it. It's all there, necromancer.
我应该相信你
I should trust you
当你不尊重我
when you when you show me no respect for me
或我迷人的超能力的时候
or my beguiling powers?
尊重一个骗子吗
Respect? For a fraud?
但你已经看到我的方法成功了
But you've seen my methods succeed.
我见识过你的魔法 有种骗人的感觉
I've seen your magic. It has a fraudulent vibe.
好了 各位 我们专注于正事吧
Okay, okay. Boys, why don't we focus?
他在跳大神
He's doing his scatting shit.
呀
Yah!
进去 你这个肮脏的混蛋
Get in, you dirty bastard!
德里克
Derek...
怎么了 伙计
What's up, dude?
好了 跟你走吧
All right. Begone with ya.
交给你了
He's all yours.
但是 如果你担心照顾不好他
But, uh, if you're worried about taking care of him,
我们有个新提议
we do have a new offer.
你当然有了
Of course you do.
-只是象征性的收费... -他开始了
For a nominal fee... Here he goes.
一个重新安置的选择
...a rehousing option.
-托弗  -不
Topher! No.
什么鬼啊
What the fuck?
谁在叫托弗
Who calls... Topher?
这吓人玩意是什么鬼
What's this "Thriller" shit?
开玩笑
Jk.
是那个人
Oh, it's that guy.
-托弗  -是的 亲爱的 你们好吗
Topher! Yeah, baby. Sup, guys?
你好吗 吉列尔莫
How you doing, Guillermo?
托弗 你看起来..
Topher, you look, uh...
-你看起来糟透了  -我是纯天然的
You look like shit. Well, I'm au naturel, babe.
我做了一些缝合工作
I've had some work done.
你知道 我还是活死人
You know, I'm still undead,
但我正在充分利用 伙计
but I'm making the most of it, man.
一旦你习惯了僵尸的身体
Once you get used to the zombie body,
你可以重新学会正常说话
you can actually learn to talk normal again.
像这样 很酷吧
Like this. Pretty cool, huh?
他只是模仿游客的口音
He just does the accent for the tourists. Eh, you know.
用了他们的一条胳膊 一条腿
Take 'em for an arm and a leg.
好了 伙计
Yeah, man.
这是谁啊
Who we got here?
-德里克  -看看这个
Der. Ek. Oh, hey, look at that.
他在努力
Yeah, he's trying.
这得花上他几个月的时间
It's gonna take him a couple months
学习如何再次正常说话
to learn how to use the ol' mouth again.
但同时 来者多多益善
But in the meantime, the more the merrier.
嘿 德里克 你想不想加入一个
Hey, Derek. How would you like to join a gang
像你这样的疯子阵营
of crazy motherfuckers just like yourself?
总会有新朋友的
There's always room for a new friend.
-朋友  -是的 朋友
Friend? Yeah. Friend!
击掌
High five!
好 需要一点时间
Oh, yeah, takes a second.
加油 伙计
Come on, buddy. Whoa!
放松 德里克
Easy, Derek.
小伙子们 给我们的新朋友德里克摆个桌位
Hey, boys, set a place at the table for our new friend Derek!
你喜欢吃人肉吗
Hey, you like eating human flesh?
你会的
Oh, you will.
非常... 酷
Very... cool.
再见 德里克 再见 德里克
Bye, Derek. Bye, Derek.
你接受Venmo支付吗
Do you take Venmo?
Venmo支付 我要现金 现金或者金币
Venmo? I take cash, hard cash or gold coin.
或者Zelle转账
Or Zelle.